[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Broadway actor in the movie Team America: World Police?", "correct_answer": "Gary", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry", "Steven", "Danny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He invented instant coffee in 1901.", "correct_answer": "Satori Koto", "incorrect_answers": ["Karl von Nestle", "Eduard Helfenmier", "Levi Hutchins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does John Candys character do for a living in the film Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Shower curtain ring salesman", "incorrect_answers": ["Insurance salesman", "Plumbing supply salesman", "Lingerie salesman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this line from the pirate freecreditreport.com commercial: They say a man should always. . .", "correct_answer": "dress for the job he wants", "incorrect_answers": ["bless corn on the cob he wants", "make a mess in the mob he haunts", "dress for the job he wins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, Rosie poses as a regular girl from this state.", "correct_answer": "Iowa", "incorrect_answers": ["Wisconsin", "Washington", "Minnesota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This type of pollutant causes acidification of rivers, lakes and also damages tree foliage and degrades soil quality.", "correct_answer": "Acid rain", "incorrect_answers": ["The melting of the poles", "The Ozone hole", "Global warming"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pong, the first commercially successful video game, is a video screen adaptation of what classic game?", "correct_answer": "Table tennis", "incorrect_answers": ["Othello", "Tic-tac-toe", "Soccer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who told Vadas dad, Harry, about Thomas J.s death in the movie My Girl?", "correct_answer": "a police officer", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas mother", "a nurse", "Shelley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You are given a bag with 10 marbles, four red marbles and six blue marbles. You select one at random. What is the probability  that the marble you select is either blue or green?", "correct_answer": "6 out of ten", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "4 out of ten", "2  out of ten"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dodgeball, Peter Le Fleur visited Kate Veatchs apartment and discovered that she had a fascination with these creatures.", "correct_answer": "unicorns", "incorrect_answers": ["rabbits", "dinosaurs", "exotic birds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What would you be eating if you were served Angels on Horseback?", "correct_answer": "Oysters wrapped in bacon", "incorrect_answers": ["Prunes wrapped in bacon", "Clams wrapped in ham", "Shrimp wrapped in chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these commands will return a Windows\u00ae computers node IP address, Subnet mask and information on whether it was assigned via DHCP and how long the lease is?", "correct_answer": "ipconfig /all", "incorrect_answers": ["ifconfig /all", "ipconfig", "ipsec /total"]}]